

# JOSE ESPINOZA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER **♦** 6472309458

• DETAILS •

6472309458 jose20019004@gmail.com

• LINKS •

**Github** 

Linkedin

• SKILLS •

MongoDB

Node.js

React

jQuery

MySQL

HTML & CSS

Git

Python

JavaScript

#### PROFILE

I have a wide set of skills from being involved in warehousing companies. I spent one year at Agrimport and one year in Bronte Import were I was the warehouse supervisor that included: -Certified Forklift Operator -Knowledgeable in computers – Oracle NetSuite, SOS Inventory, Zoho Inventory and Java. -Well-organized, detailed approach to work. -Leadership skills. -Works well within a team environment. -Articulates instructions clearly. After my studies I have Full Stack Web Development.

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### Warehouse Supervisor at Agrimport, Mississauga

January 2020 — July 2021

I was the warehouse supervisor that included: -Certified Forklift Operator -Knowledgeable in computers – Oracle NetSuite, SOS Inventory, Zoho Inventory and Java. -Well-organized, detailed approach to work. -Leadership skills. -Works well within a team environment. -Articulates instructions clearly.

# Warehouse Supervisor at Bronte Import, Oakville

September 2020 — January 2021

I was the warehouse supervisor that included: -Certified Forklift Operator -Knowledgeable in computers – Oracle NetSuite, SOS Inventory, Zoho Inventory and Java. -Well-organized, detailed approach to work. -Leadership skills. -Works well within a team environment. -Articulates instructions clearly.

## EDUCATION

Certificate, University of Toronto, Toronto

February 2021 — April 2021